[
    {
        "answer": "ballot",
        "question": "The opposition proposed to deface the {...} papers",
        "options": ["voting", "election", "electoral"]
    },
    {
        "answer": "plastic",
        "question": "a red {...} car",
        "options": ["fast", "small", "good"]
    },
    {
        "answer": "avenge",
        "question": "<strong>To get back at</strong> means to {...}",
        "options": ["return", "rebate", "descend"]
    },
    {
        "answer": "at",
        "question": "To critize is to get {...}",
        "options": ["by", "off", "out"]
    },
    {
        "answer": "have you known",
        "question": "How long {} him?",
        "options": ["you have knowing", "you know", "you knew"]
    },
    {
        "answer": "lose",
        "question": "To get down <strong>doesn't mean</strong> to {}",
        "options": ["dance", "reduce", "write"]
    },
    {
        "answer": "a means to an end",
        "question": "It's nothing personal, but it was {...}",
        "options": ["the mean to an end", "mean to an end", "means to end"]
    },
    {
        "answer": "hit",
        "question": "A synonym for \"clout\" is {...}",
        "options": ["bar", "truck", "explore"]
    },
    {
        "answer": "attack",
        "question": "an asthma {...}",
        "options": ["fit", "bout", "seizure"]
    },
    {
        "answer": "a vehicle used for carrying the coffin",
        "question": "A hearse is {...}",
        "options": ["a type of a sail", "a feeling of great worry or unhappiness", "an area that somebody cannot see"]
    }
]